(Sheldon:)Oh, come on, Leonard...
(Sheldon:)This is obviously about Penny.
(Leonard:)It doesn't matter.
(Leonard:)The woman's not interested in me.
The woman rejected me.
Okay, look. Ahem.
(Sheldon:)You have as much of a chance of having
a sexual relationship with Penny...
(Sheldon:)...as the Hubble telescope does...
(Sheldon:)...of discovering
at the center of every black hole...
(Sheldon:)...is a little man with a flashlight
searching for a circuit breaker.
(Sheldon:)Nevertheless, I do feel obligated
to point out to you...
...that she did not reject you.
(Sheldon:)You did not ask her out.
(Leonard:)You're right.
I didn't ask her. I should ask her out.
(Sheldon:)No, no. Now, that was not my point.
(Sheldon:)My point was, don't buy a cat.
(Leonard:)No, but you're right.
(Leonard:)I should march over there
and ask her out.
(Sheldon:)Oh, goody, we're getting a cat.
(Leonard:)Oh, yeah... No.